<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="daftarras">Animal Race List</string>
    <string name="hewanpedia">AnimalsPedia</string>
    <string name="jenis_jenis">Types</string>
    <string name="pri00">Primates</string>
    <string name="el00">Hawk</string>
    <string name="hiu00">Shark</string>
    <string name="ket">(Tap on the animal image to open the gallery)</string>
    <string name="pri1">Sumatran Orangutan</string>
    <string name="pen1">Animals that eat fruits such as mango, jackfruit, durian and lychee. In addition, the Sumatran Orangutan also eats eggs and small vertebrates.</string>
    <string name="pri2">Makinobu or Pig-tailed Langur</string>
    <string name="asal2">Mentawai Islands</string>
    <string name="pen2">Makinobu is a member of the ape family. The population is 6,700–17,300 individuals (IUCN, 2006). The current status of the Sisiobu is as a rare animal.</string>
    <string name="pri3">Sulawesi Black Monkey or yaki</string>
    <string name="pen3">Yaki or wolai monkeys or Sulawesi black monkeys (Macaca nigra) / red-rumped monkeys are endemic to Indonesia which are only found on the northern part of Sulawesi Island and several surrounding islands, namely in the Tangkoko Bitung Forest.</string>
    <string name="pri4">Proboscis monkey</string>
    <string name="asal4">Borneo</string>
    <string name="pen4">Proboscis monkeys are monkeys that have long noses and animals that eat seeds and fruits. It can also eat leaves which can produce gas when digested.</string>
    <string name="pri5">Mentawai Beruk</string>
    <string name="asal5">Mentawai Islands</string>
    <string name="pen5">Local people call it Bokoi or bokkoi (Macaca pagensis). They are a type of monkey that is limited (endemic) to the Mentawai Islands, off the west coast of Sumatra.</string>
    <string name="el1">Black Eagle</string>
    <string name="as1">tropical Asia</string>
    <string name="penj1">The black eagle is a species of eagle with great defensive power and is spread over various areas at an altitude of three hundred to two thousand meters above sea level. The special characteristics of the black eagle are seen from its wings that appear to be fingered, wide and strong.</string>
    <string name="el2">Brontok Eagle</string>
    <string name="as2">Sumatra, Kalimantan, Java, Bali and Nusa Tenggara</string>
    <string name="penj2">The brontok eagle is a type of bird of prey belonging to the Accipitridae tribe. It is so named possibly because of its speckled color (in light-colored forms).</string>
    <string name="el3">Javanese Eagle</string>
    <string name="as3">Java</string>
    <string name="penj3">The Javan eagle lives in the inland and secondary zones at an altitude of 3 hundred above sea level.</string>
    <string name="el4">Bido Snake Eagle</string>
    <string name="penj4">Also known as the Crested Serpent Eagle or CSE by some bird of prey (BOP) lovers</string>
    <string name="el5">Short Finger Snake Eagle</string>
    <string name="as5">traveler</string>
    <string name="penj5">The short fingered snake eagle is a large animal with a dimension of 65 centimeters. His body is mighty with a white fur color. The animal is very rarely seen.</string>
    <string name="h1">Goblin Shark</string>
    <string name="fr1">Indo-Pacific and Oceania</string>
    <string name="p1">Judging from its appearance alone, this one shark already looks terrible. How not, he has horns on his forehead, unlike sharks in general.</string>
    <string name="h2">Great White Shark</string>
    <string name="fr2">coastal waters throughout the main ocean surface</string>
    <string name="p2">The Great White Shark is the largest flesh-eating shark in the world. The females can grow up to six meters, while the male sharks can grow up to four meters. They can be found throughout the oceans, but mostly occupy warm areas.</string>
    <string name="h3">bull shark</string>
    <string name="fr3">North to South America</string>
    <string name="p3">Bull sharks have a relatively small body, ranging from two to three meters. But don\'t underestimate them. The bull shark is often referred to as the most dangerous shark in the world.</string>
    <string name="h4">tiger shark</string>
    <string name="fr4">Indian Ocean waters.</string>
    <string name="p4">Tiger sharks have a reputation for being man-eaters. They are the second most dangerous shark after the bull shark. Its body is quite large because it can grow up to five meters long.</string>
    <string name="h5">Hammerhead shark</string>
    <string name="fr5">Indian Ocean south of Java and Nusa Tenggara.</string>
    <string name="p5">The hammerhead shark is famous for its unique head shape. They are also quite large because they can grow up to six meters long.</string>
    <string name="name_Elang">Different Kinds of Eagle</string>
    <string name="name_Hiu">Different Kinds of Shark</string>
    <string name="name_primata">Different Kinds of Primates</string>
    <string name="app_name">ariadi</string>
    <string name="tt">About Creator</string>
</resources>